A Guide to the Robert and Wilva Breen Collection, 1933-1980
George Mason University Libraries
- The Robert Breen Collection
  - REGIONAL INFO 1947., Folder 7 (Box Box 64)
  - REGIONAL THEATRES 1947., Folder 8 (Box Box 64)
  - PUBLIC RELEASES 1947., Folder 9 (Box Box 64)
  - EARLY ANTA (ARTICLES AND NEWSPAPER PUBLICATION)., Folder 10 (Box Box 64)
  - BOOKING INFO - CORRESPONDENCE 1948., Folder 11 (Box Box 64)
  - ANTA PROGRAMS SUMMER 1948., Folder 12 (Box Box 64)
  - ANTA - REGISTRY, OBJECTIVES, SERVICES ETC., Folder 13 (Box Box 64)
  - ANTA REQUESTS FROM THE FIELD 1948., Folder 14 (Box Box 64)
  - ANTA ACTIVITIES AND INCREASING PRESTIGE 1948 - 49 (TWO LETTERS RELATING TO TOLEDO OHIO., Folder 15 (Box Box 64)
  - TOURING COMPANIES '48., Folder 1 (Box Box 65)
  - MANAGEMENT TRAINING - CORRESPONDENCE., Folder 2 (Box Box 65)
  - COMMUNITY THEATER MATERIALS., Folder 3 (Box Box 65)
  - DRAMATICS VOLUME. XX. NO. 5 FEB 1949., Folder 4 (Box Box 65)
  - ANTA FOURTH ANNUAL CHILDREN THEATER CONFERENCE OF THE AMERICAN EDUCATION., Folder 5 (Box Box 65)
  - LIST OF UNIVERSITY AND REGIONAL THEATER GROUPS., Folder 6 (Box Box 65)
  - LIST OF UNIVERSITY AND REGIONAL THEATER GROUPS., Folder 7 (Box Box 65)
  - ANTA MISC. MAPS BOOKLETS., Folder 8 (Box Box 65)
  - R. B. / HOLD - BREEN., Folder 9 (Box Box 65)
  - R. B. / HOLD - BREEN., Folder 10 (Box Box 65)
  - THEATER ARTS REPRINT JAN. 1949., Folder 11 (Box Box 65)
  - MAILING LISTS 1949 - 50., Folder 12 (Box Box 65)
  - THEATER COUNCIL FOR NORTHERN CALIFORNIA AND NEVADA REGIONAL COUNCIL OF ANTA., Folder 13 (Box Box 65)
  - CONTINUOUS DEPARTMENTAL WORKS AND ANTA SERVICES TO THE THEATER EVERY WHERE (TWO PAPERS)., Folder 14 (Box Box 65)
  - "AT THE THEATER" BY ATKINSON REPRINTS 1950., Folder 1 (Box Box 66)
  - AWARDS COHEN PROPOSAL 1950 - 51., Folder 2 (Box Box 66)
  - RECOMMENDATIONS OF ANTA WORK 1950 - 51., Folder 3 (Box Box 66)
  - PLAY LIST., Folder 4 (Box Box 66)
  - ANTA FORMS, INTERNATIONAL THEATER MONTH 1951., Folder 5 (Box Box 66)
  - PITTISBURGH - GABRIEL RUBIN., Folder 6 (Box Box 66)
  - RUMOR 1951., Folder 7 (Box Box 66)
  - SERIGRAPH., Folder 8 (Box Box 66)
  - THEATER OF AMERICA 1951., Folder 9 (Box Box 66)
  - INTERNATIONAL MISC., Folder 10 (Box Box 66)
  - BROCHURE BENJAMIN KAYE., Folder 11 (Box Box 66)
  - GENERAL ANTA "40 THEATER" PLAN 1957., Folder 1 (Box Box 67)
  - NEWSLETTERS 1959., Folder 2 (Box Box 67)
  - ANTA - LIST OF PLAYS FROM COMPILATIONS BY Dr. JOHN REICH., Folder 3 (Box Box 67)
  - "NAT'L THEATER PLANS TO RESUME" CLIPPINGS., Folder 4 (Box Box 67)
  - "SIX 0' CLOCK THEATER" AMPLET., Folder 5 (Box Box 67)
  - CARD CATALOG RELATING TO THE THEATER., Folder 5 (Box Box 67)
  - FUNDING., Folder 6 (Box Box 67)
  - ANTA - DECCA RECORDS "ALBUM OF STARS"., Folder 7 (Box Box 67)
  - ANTA - BULLET; '45., Folder 1 (Box Box 68)
  - ROOSEVELT - PORTFIELD MEETING., Folder 2 (Box Box 68)
  - THEATER ARTS - OSCAR SERLIN ARTICLE 1945., Folder 3 (Box Box 68)
  - MEMBERSHIP 1947., Folder 4 (Box Box 68)
  - ANTA - NEWSLETTER 1947., Folder 5 (Box Box 68)
  - ANTA - NEWSLETTER 1948., Folder 6 (Box Box 68)
  - ANTA - NEWSLETTER 1949., Folder 7 (Box Box 68)
  - ANTA - NEWSLETTER 1950., Folder 8 (Box Box 68)
  - NATHAN REPORT 4/48., Folder 9 (Box Box 68)
  - NATHAN REPORT 1948 FOR SURVEYING THE LEGITIMATE THEATER., Folder 10 (Box Box 68)
  - IDEAS AND OUTLINES 1949., Folder 11 (Box Box 68)
  - THEATER DEVELOPMENT (W.D)., Folder 12 (Box Box 68)
  - "COUNCIL OF LIVING THEATER"., Folder 13 (Box Box 68)
  - EARLY ANTA., Folder 14 (Box Box 68)
  - ANTA MISC. 1952., Folder 15 (Box Box 68)
  - SUPPORT LIST., Folder 16 (Box Box 68)
  - WORLD THEATER., Folder 17 (Box Box 68)
  - NOTES ON CONFERENCE HELD IN ALAN CORELLI'S., Folder 1 (Box Box 69)
  - STEERING COMMITTEE MEETINGS REGARDING THE CONFERENCE OF THEATER SUBJECT., Folder 2 (Box Box 69)
  - ANTA - NATIONAL THEATER ASSEMBLY 1950 - 51., Folder 3 (Box Box 69)
  - 2ND DRAFT ASSEMBLY REPORT NATIONAL THEATER ASSEMBLY., Folder 4 (Box Box 69)
  - ANTA MISC LETTERS AND BILLS., Folder 5 (Box Box 69)
  - NAT'L THEATER ASSEMBLY JAN. 1951., Folder 6 (Box Box 69)
  - THEATER ASSEMBLY., Folder 7 (Box Box 69)
  - NAT'L THEATER ASSEMBLY COMMENTS., Folder 8 (Box Box 69)
  - ANTA - MULTIP - COP., Folder 9 (Box Box 69)
  - ANTA - SERVICES AND STAFF CUTS., Folder 10 (Box Box 69)
  - PLANS FOR NATIONAL THEATER ASSEMBLE AND ANTA BOOKLETS 1948., Folder 11 (Box Box 69)
  - THEATER NEWS WEEKLY 1/5/51., Folder 12 (Box Box 69)
  - GENERAL LIST OF PLAYS AND ACTORS., Folder 1 (Box Box 70)
  - 1948; PRES. REPORT; CHILDREN'S THEATER DIRECTORY., Folder 2 (Box Box 70)
  - NOTES ON THE OPERATION OF THE ANTA PLAYHOUSE., Folder 3 (Box Box 70)
  - ANTA MISC., Folder 4 (Box Box 70)
  - ANTA PLAYHOUSE AND SERIES., Folder 5 (Box Box 70)
  - NY CITY CENTER - HOUSED IN THE ANTA PLAYHOUSE., Folder 6 (Box Box 70)
  - ANTA - PLAYHOUSE SPACE ALLOTMENTS., Folder 7 (Box Box 70)
  - ANTA - PLAYHOUSE (TELEGRAMS; '51)., Folder 8 (Box Box 70)
  - LISTS OF S.A.G; PLAYS AND PEOPLE., Folder 9 (Box Box 70)
  - OLIVIER., Folder 10 (Box Box 70)
  - " THE ROYAL FAMILY" ACYED BY FLORANCE REED UNIVERSITY OF UTAH, 1949., Folder 11 (Box Box 70)
  - "TEMPEST" AT PLAYHOUSE., Folder 12 (Box Box 70)
  - ANTA - PLAYHOUSE., Folder 13 (Box Box 70)
  - "NIGHT MUSIC" AT PLAYHOUSE., Folder 14 (Box Box 70)
  - BLANCHE YURKA., Folder 15 (Box Box 70)
  - CORRESPONDENCE - ACTIVE IRVING PLACE., Folder 1 (Box Box 71)
  - ARTISTS APPEARING ON "THEATER, USA"., Folder 2 (Box Box 71)
  - TV HARRITY - ROOSEVELT JONES 1950-51., Folder 3 (Box Box 71)
  - TELEVISION: HAMITY STAGG., Folder 4 (Box Box 71)
  - TELEVISION AND RADIO., Folder 5 (Box Box 71)
  - AGREEMENT FROM ANTA AND ACTORS., Folder 6 (Box Box 71)
  - PLAN FOR PUBLIC THEATER FOUNDATION (RB)., Folder 7 (Box Box 71)
  - MEMO FROM JUDITH ANDERSON., Folder 8 (Box Box 71)
  - PLANS FOR ANTA TV/M. CISNEY., Folder 9 (Box Box 71)
  - LIST OF TECHNICIANS, YALE DRAMA SCHOOL., Folder 10 (Box Box 71)
  - ANTA - PRESENTATIONS., Folder 1 (Box Box 72)
  - ANTA PRESENTATIONS 1947., Folder 2 (Box Box 72)
  - PUBLICITY - BROCHURES SAMPLES., Folder 3 (Box Box 72)
  - "IMPT. PRINCIPLES IN FURNISHING TROOP ENTERTAINMENT"., Folder 4 (Box Box 72)
  - OBJECTIVES OF ANTA, RELATING TO THE TROOP ENTERTAINMENT PROGRAMS FOR THE DEPARTMENT OF DEFENCE., Folder 5 (Box Box 72)
  - ANTA OVERSEAS ENTERTAINMENT., Folder 6 (Box Box 72)
  - TROOP ENTERTAINMENT / ANTAS THEATER USA., Folder 7 (Box Box 72)
  - TROOP SHOWS - SENATE., Folder 8 (Box Box 72)
  - TROOP ENTERTAINMENT - STARS., Folder 9 (Box Box 72)
  - ANTA AS PARENT BODY FOR EXPANDING TROOP ENTERTAIN., Folder 10 (Box Box 72)
  - ANTA SPEAKERS BUREAU., Folder 11 (Box Box 72)
  - COPIES OF NEWS CLIPS RE NAT. THEATER PLAN., Folder 12 (Box Box 72)
  - ORGANIZATIONS - UNITED NATIONS COMMITTEE., Folder 1 (Box Box 73)
  - AUTHOR'S LEAGUE BULLETIN SEPT. 1946., Folder 2 (Box Box 73)
  - "UNESCO AND YOU"., Folder 3 (Box Box 73)
  - UNESCO - PROGRAM - 2ND SESS. OF GEN CONF., Folder 4 (Box Box 73)
  - UNESCO ROSAMOND GILDER - THEATER INTERNATIONAL., Folder 5 (Box Box 73)
  - UNESCO - INV. TO THEATER DIRECTIONS FROM GILDER., Folder 6 (Box Box 73)
  - TROOP ENTERTAINMENTS CORRESPONDENCE., Folder 7 (Box Box 73)
  - MEMO, NEWS AND ARTICLES, PRESENTATION ETC., Folder 8 (Box Box 73)
  - ANTA - MULTIP - COP., Folder 9 (Box Box 73)
  - PROMOTION OF "DEATH OF A SALESMAN"., Folder 10 (Box Box 73)
  - PHONEVISION, I V. OPPORTUNITIES., Folder 11 (Box Box 73)
  - PHONEVISION, TELEVISION, SATURDAY REVIEW ETC., Folder 12 (Box Box 73)
  - HELEN HAYES (PUBLIC RELATIONS)., Folder 13 (Box Box 73)
  - OUTGOING ANTA CORRESPONDENCE 1951 FEB/MAR., Folder 14 (Box Box 73)
  - PROMOTION OF "BILLY BUD" 1951., Folder 15 (Box Box 73)
  - PROMOTION OF DEATH OF A SALESMAN., Folder 16 (Box Box 73)
  - ANTA PRE - SALES PLAN., Folder 17 (Box Box 73)
  - ANTA LATER - " CHAPTER ONE" - PAPER PUB. BY ANTA N.Y. CHAPTER., Folder 18 (Box Box 73)
  - PROGRAMS OF ANTA - TO MEMBERS OF ANTA., Folder 19 (Box Box 73)
  - GETTING MARRIED 1950., Folder 1 (Box Box 74)
  - "GETTING MARRIED"., Folder 2 (Box Box 74)
  - ANTA PLAYHOUSE GETTING MARRIED., Folder 3 (Box Box 74)
  - "GETTING MARRIED"., Folder 4 (Box Box 74)
  - GETTING MARRIED / PARTIES., Folder 5 (Box Box 74)
  - GETTING MARRIED - TOURS., Folder 6 (Box Box 74)
  - "GETTING MARRIED" - TOUR., Folder 7 (Box Box 74)
  - GETTING MARRIED / SUMMER PROD. '51., Folder 8 (Box Box 74)
  - WARNER WATSON FILE MARKED "PERSONAL"., Folder 9 (Box Box 74)
  - PRESS LISTS., Folder 10 (Box Box 74)
  - WARNER WATSON - LISTS., Folder 11 (Box Box 74)
  - WARNER WATSON NOTES., Folder 12 (Box Box 74)
  - WATSON WARNER (LISTS OF CRITICS IN REGIONS)., Folder 13 (Box Box 74)
  - FUND RAISING: FOUNDATIONS., Folder 1 (Box Box 75)
  - FINANCE - MISC CORRESPONDENCE., Folder 2 (Box Box 75)
  - FUND RAISING: ROCKEFELLER FOUNDATION - CORRESPONDENCE 1946 - 1947., Folder 3 (Box Box 75)
  - FUND RAISING: FOUNDATIONS CLIPPINGS., Folder 4 (Box Box 75)
  - FUND RAISING: FOUNDATIONS CORRESPONDENCE 1947 - 1950., Folder 5 (Box Box 75)
  - FUND RAISING: FOUNDATION: ROCKEFELLER, CORRESPONDENCE., Folder 6 (Box Box 75)
  - FINANCES: BANK BALANCER., Folder 7 (Box Box 75)
  - FINANCIAL REPORTS: MEMOS., Folder 8 (Box Box 75)
  - FUND RAISING: FOUNDATIONS ROCKEFELLER FOUNDATION., Folder 9 (Box Box 75)
  - FOUNDATIONS - FORD., Folder 10 (Box Box 75)
  - FUND RAISING CORRESPONDENCE., Folder 11 (Box Box 75)
  - FUNDING., Folder 12 (Box Box 75)
  - ROCKEFELLER FOUNDATION., Folder 13 (Box Box 75)
  - ANTA NEWS CLIPPINGS., Folder 14 (Box Box 75)
  - FOUNDATION - WHITNEY., Folder 15 (Box Box 75)
  - ANTA - FINANCIAL STATEMENT., Folder 16 (Box Box 75)
  - PRODUCTION COST., Folder 17 (Box Box 75)
  - ANGELS., Folder 1 (Box Box 76)
  - PLAN TO INCREASE THEATER TICKET SALES AND COMMITTEE., Folder 2 (Box Box 76)
  - FUND RAISING / BEAUX ARTS BALL., Folder 3 (Box Box 76)
  - "ANGELS" FUNDING., Folder 4 (Box Box 76)
  - ANTA - PREVIEW FOR PATRONS - A PUBLICATIONS TO ATTRACT THE PEOPLE FOR FUNDING., Folder 5 (Box Box 76)
  - ANTA - PLAYHOUSE - CADILLAC (1950)., Folder 6 (Box Box 76)
  - FUNDING 1950' - 51' PLAY SERIES., Folder 7 (Box Box 76)
  - FUNDING 1950' - 51' PLAY SERIES., Folder 8 (Box Box 76)
  - FUNDING - 1950' - 51' PLAY SERIES., Folder 1 (Box Box 77)
  - FUNDING - 1950' - 51' PLAY SERIES, Folder 2 (Box Box 77)
  - FUNDING - 1950' - 51' PLAY SERIES, Folder 3 (Box Box 77)
  - FUND CAMPAIGN., Folder 4 (Box Box 77)
  - FUNDING - CAMPAIGN AND OTHER EFFORTS., Folder 5 (Box Box 77)
  - ANTA - MEMO MEETING WITH Mr. MITCHAL OF CHEMICAL BANK., Folder 6 (Box Box 77)
  - FUNDING CAMPAIGN., Folder 7 (Box Box 77)
  - INDICATION OF TAX METHOD USED IN OTHER COUNTRIES TO PROVIDE FUNDS FOR NATIONAL OR STATES THEATER AND COUNCIL FOR ENCOURAGEMENT OF MUSIC AND ARTS., Folder 8 (Box Box 77)
  - FUNDING - 1950 - '51 PLAY SERIES., Folder 1 (Box Box 78)
  - FUND DRIVE - DOWLING MEETINGS., Folder 2 (Box Box 78)
  - FUND RAISING / BEAUX ARTS BALL., Folder 3 (Box Box 78)
  - FUND RAISING - BEAUX ART BALL., Folder 4 (Box Box 78)
  - "CELEBRITY CORNER" ARTICLE RE ANTA FUND CAMPAIGN., Folder 5 (Box Box 78)
  - PROGRAM FOR A NATIONAL THEATER FOUNDATION AND FUND AND SUMMARY OF PROCEDURE TO PROVIDE NECESSARY FUNDS., Folder 1 (Box Box 79)
  - A LETTER REGARDING TO INCOME TAX AND INTERNAL REVENUE OF ANTA AND CBS, NOV. 6, 1947., Folder 2 (Box Box 79)
  - FUNDING., Folder 3 (Box Box 79)
  - EXPERIMENTAL THEATER AND ANTA FINANCIAL STATEMENTS 1947 - 48., Folder 4 (Box Box 79)
  - FINANCIAL RECORDS (EXP. THEATERS 1947- 48)., Folder 5 (Box Box 79)
  - ANTA FUND CAMPAIGN - FINANCIAL STATEMENT., Folder 6 (Box Box 79)
  - ANN. REPTS. INCL. FINANCIAL STATEMENTS., Folder 7 (Box Box 79)
  - FUNDING - FINANCIAL STATEMENTS., Folder 8 (Box Box 79)
  - FINANCIAL REPORTS - MONTHLY STATEMENTS., Folder 9 (Box Box 79)
  - FINANCIAL REPORTS :QUARTERLY STATEMENTS., Folder 10 (Box Box 79)
  - FUNDING - FINANCIAL STATEMENTS., Folder 11 (Box Box 79)
  - FINANCIAL REPORTS: COMPARATIVE REPORTS., Folder 12 (Box Box 79)
  - FINANCIAL REPORTS: MONTHLY ESTIMATES., Folder 13 (Box Box 79)
  - FINANCIAL REPORTS - MONTHLY STATEMENTS., Folder 14 (Box Box 79)
  - FINANCIAL STATEMENT 1949., Folder 15 (Box Box 79)
  - RFC BUSINESS LOAN APPLICATION., Folder 16 (Box Box 79)
  - STATEMENT OF TICKET SALES - BALTIMORE THEATER, " GETTING MARRIED", JUNE, 1950., Folder 17 (Box Box 79)
  - ANTA ALBUM FINANCIAL STATEMENTS 1951., Folder 18 (Box Box 79)
  - FINANCIAL: OFFICE OPERATION., Folder 19 (Box Box 79)
  - FINANCIAL STATEMENTS PLAY SERIES., Folder 20 (Box Box 79)
  - ANTA - THEATER BILL., Folder 21 (Box Box 79)
  - OFFICE., Folder 22 (Box Box 79)
  - 1951 PAYMENT BY GUEST PROCEDURES OF AVERAGES IN OPERATION COSTS., Folder 23 (Box Box 79)
  - THEATRICAL EQUIPMENT OF THE C.C.S.S. AND A.A.T. STARTED AT N.V., Folder 1 (Box Box 80)
  - ANTA PLAY HOUSE - EQUIPMENT., Folder 2 (Box Box 80)
  - I.E.P. PRES. EISENHOWER (DU PLICATER - ORIGINAL TO OHIO STATE UNIVERSITY., Folder 3 (Box Box 80)
  - DU PLICATER - ORIGINAL TO OHIO., Folder 4 (Box Box 80)
  - GOVERNMENT., Folder 5 (Box Box 80)
  - EVERY MAN OPERA CO. CORRESPONDENCE JUNE - NOV. 1954 (COPIER)., Folder 6 (Box Box 80)
  - ANTA AND EVERY MAN OPERA CO. CORRESPONDENCE, DECEMBER 1954 (COPIES)., Folder 7 (Box Box 80)
  - ANTA AND EVERY MAN OPERA CO. CORRESPONDENCE JAN. - FEB. 1955., Folder 8 (Box Box 80)
  - ANTA AND EVERY MAN OPERA CO. CORRESPONDENCE JAN. - FEB. 1955, Folder 9 (Box Box 80)
  - DEP'T. OF STATE LTR, 12 MA '55., Folder 10 (Box Box 80)
  - GENERAL ANTA (MID EAST)., Folder 11 (Box Box 80)
  - STARK, JOHN PLUS R.B. CORRESPONDENCE., Folder 12 (Box Box 80)
  - CENTURY FIGHTING 1955 - 56., Folder 13 (Box Box 80)
  - I.E.P. EXCA PROG. (DUPLICATOR - ORIGINAL TO OHIO STATE)., Folder 14 (Box Box 80)
  - ANTA EVERYMAN OCT. 1957., Folder 15 (Box Box 80)
  - I.E.P. 1955 - 56 - 57 (DUPLICATOR - ORIGINAL TO OHIO STATE), Folder 16 (Box Box 80)
  - ANTA C/A/AM., Folder 17 (Box Box 80)
  - ANTA VS. EVERY MAN OPERA., Folder 18 (Box Box 80)
  - LETTERS TO CARL SCHAEFFER., Folder 19 (Box Box 80)
  - SHULL., Folder 20 (Box Box 80)
  - "THE GHOST OF WOODROW WILSON" BY GERALD W. JOHNSON., Folder 1 (Box Box 81)
  - MORALE - REGARDING WAR., Folder 2 (Box Box 81)
  - THE PEACE / AVOID THE NEXT WAR., Folder 3 (Box Box 81)
  - ELY CULBERTSON - THE WORLD FEDERATION, PLAN AND WORLD FEDERATION INC., Folder 4 (Box Box 81)
  - FREE WORLD ORGANIZATION., Folder 5 (Box Box 81)
  - WAR PEACE FREEDOM HOUSE - ORGANIZATION 1943 AND FREE WORLD., Folder 6 (Box Box 81)
  - NATIONAL WOMEN'S PARTY ORGANIZATION., Folder 7 (Box Box 81)
  - "UNKNOWN SOLDIER"., Folder 8 (Box Box 81)
  - POST WAR ORGANIZATIONS - GENERAL (WIN THE PEACE)., Folder 9 (Box Box 81)
  - PEACE 1943., Folder 10 (Box Box 81)
  - SENATE RESOLUTION 114 #2 OF 2 REFERED TO THE COMMITTEE ON FOREIGN RELATIONS., Folder 11 (Box Box 81)
  - INDEPENDENT REPUBLICANS., Folder 12 (Box Box 81)
  - AMERICANS UNITED FOR THE ESTABLISHMENT OF WORLD ORG., Folder 13 (Box Box 81)
  - WORLD - ORGANIZATION - MRS. CLYDE., Folder 14 (Box Box 81)
  - "WOODROW WILSON" SCRIPT CLIPPINGS., Folder 15 (Box Box 81)
  - CLIPPINGS (WAR)., Folder 16 (Box Box 81)
  - WAR - SENATORS CLIPPINGS 1943., Folder 17 (Box Box 81)
  - CONTRIBUTION OF THEATER IN THE WAR EFFORT., Folder 18 (Box Box 81)
  - TIMETABLES AND MAPS (MILITARY AND NAVAL) WAR TIME., Folder 19 (Box Box 81)
  - NEW YORK MIRROR WEEKLY JOURNAL APRIL 26, 1834., Folder 1 (Box Box 82)
  - THEATER GUILD 20TH BROCHURE., Folder 2 (Box Box 82)
  - PRE - ANTA PUBLICATION M - DAY 1940., Folder 3 (Box Box 82)
  - POST WAR PLANNING IN THE U.S. 1943., Folder 4 (Box Box 82)
  - ARTICLES OF THE AMERICAN SOC. OF COMPOSERS, AUTHORS ANS PUBLISHERS 1944., Folder 5 (Box Box 82)
  - TELEVISION: BOOKLETS PLANNING YOUR TELEVISION STATION AND TELEVISION W RGB AND SAVE OTHERS., Folder 6 (Box Box 82)
  - EQUITY MAGAZINE / JAN. 1946, MAY 1947., Folder 7 (Box Box 82)
  - BOOK ON DENMARK - MARKS BY BREEN FOR CASTLES., Folder 8 (Box Box 82)
  - MISC. CIVIC ENTERTAINMENT VOL. 1 NOV. - DEC. 1948., Folder 9 (Box Box 82)
  - DENMARK., Folder 10 (Box Box 82)
  - LOOSE MTLS., Folder 11 (Box Box 82)
  - "DECLINE OF THE PROFESSIONAL THEATER IN AMER". THE QUARTERLY JOURNAL OF SPEECH., Folder 1 (Box Box 83)
  - GUIDE - PANORAMA OF THE RHINE AND MALERIER AT THE TIME OF HAMLET IN EUROPE., Folder 2 (Box Box 83)
  - NEWS FROM HOME VOL. X, NO-1. FEB. MARCH - 1949., Folder 3 (Box Box 83)
  - MISC. PRINTED BOOKLETS., Folder 4 (Box Box 83)
  - CUE - SEPT. 1950 (THE MAGAZINE OF NEW YORK LIVING)., Folder 5 (Box Box 83)
  - THE NEW YORK VISITOR APRIL 1951, Folder 6 (Box Box 83)
  - COMMUNITY THEATER BULLETIN, DEC. 1951., Folder 7 (Box Box 83)
  - THEATER NEWS LETTER VOL. 6 NO. 128 AUG, 4TH 1951., Folder 8 (Box Box 83)
  - WHITE BARN THEATER AND YOUNG IRELAND THEATER COMPANY., Folder 9 (Box Box 83)
  - ANTA - NEWS FEB. 1953., Folder 10 (Box Box 83)
  - PRINTED MATERIALS (MAGAZINES)., Folder 11 (Box Box 83)
  - PORGY AND BESS 1954 - 55., Folder 12 (Box Box 83)
  - "ANTA THE FOUNTAINHEAD" REPRINTED FROM NEWS FROM HOME., Folder 13 (Box Box 83)
  - BOOKS ON CZECNOSLOVAKIA (BARRANDA) DENMARK (KRONBORG) KRONBORG CASTLE PHOTO YUGOSLOVIA (PUBROVNIK)., Folder 14 (Box Box 83)
  - MISC. PLAYBILL - THE INTERNATIONAL MAGAZINE FOR THE THEATER. A PUBLICATION OF HALEN HAYES THEATER., Folder 15 (Box Box 83)
  - VARIOUS CLIPS 1934 - 1935 (ROMEO AND JULIET, HAMLET AND IVERY DOOR)., Folder 1 (Box Box 84)
  - MISC. BOX 1946 (BREEN)., Folder 2 (Box Box 84)
  - THE BILL BOARD (AUG 21, 1948)., Folder 3 (Box Box 84)
  - ANTA (CLIPPINGS)., Folder 4 (Box Box 84)
  - VARIETY (APRIL 13, 1949)., Folder 1 (Box Box 85)
  - MISC. ANTA 1949 - 50 (CLIPPINGS)., Folder 2 (Box Box 85)
  - BALLET THEATER TOUR 1950 FROM BOX F -III., Folder 3 (Box Box 85)
  - THEATER NEWS WEEKLY EDITORIAL ON ANTA OCT, 6TH 1950 AND MESSAGES FROM NY FROM H. HAYES 12/29/1950.SHOW BUSINESS, Folder 4 (Box Box 85)
  - NOV. 13TH 1950 SHOW BUSINESS BREEN AND ANTA NEWS., Folder 5 (Box Box 85)
  - REVIEWS FOR BOOK., Folder 6 (Box Box 85)
  - ANTA 1951 - BREENS RESIGNATION (CLIPPINGS)., Folder 7 (Box Box 85)
  - ANTA MISC. (CLIPPINGS)., Folder 8 (Box Box 85)
  - ANTA NEW YORK TIMES (CLIPPINGS)., Folder 9 (Box Box 85)
  - MISC. ANTA (CLIPPINGS)., Folder 10 (Box Box 85)
  - ANTA 1951 - 51 (CLIPPINGS)., Folder 11 (Box Box 85)
  - ANTA ALBUM (CLIPPINGS)., Folder 1 (Box Box 86)
  - PLAY SERIES 1950., Folder 2 (Box Box 86)
  - MISC. ANTA PLAYS (CLIPPINGS) 1950., Folder 3 (Box Box 86)
  - PLAY SERIES SEPT '50 (CLIPPINGS) (BROADWAY REPORTER) PLUS )BROOKLYN EAGLES)., Folder 4 (Box Box 86)
  - MISC. 1951 MISC. ANTA PLAY (CLIPPINGS)., Folder 5 (Box Box 86)
  - WARNEN WEAN DAILY - ON ANTA PLAY SERIES., Folder 6 (Box Box 86)
  - MISC ANTA PLAYS (CLIPPINGS)., Folder 7 (Box Box 86)
  - MISC. ANTA PLAY SERIES., Folder 1 (Box Box 87)
  - MISC. ANTA PLAY SERIES, Folder 2 (Box Box 87)
  - MISC. ANTA PLAY SERIES, Folder 3 (Box Box 87)
  - MISC. ANTA PLAY SERIES, Folder 4 (Box Box 87)
  - MISC. ANTA PLAY SERIES, Folder 5 (Box Box 87)
  - MISC. ANTA PLAY SERIES, Folder 6 (Box Box 87)
  - MISC. ANTA PLAY SERIES, Folder 7 (Box Box 87)
  - ANTA PLAY SERIES., Folder 1 (Box Box 88)
  - ANTA PLAYHOUSE PLUS SERIES., Folder 2 (Box Box 88)
  - THE CELLAR AND THE WELL., Folder 3 (Box Box 88)
  - THE CELLAR AND THE WELL., Folder 4 (Box Box 88)
  - THE CELLAR AND THE WELL., Folder 5 (Box Box 88)
  - TWENTIETH CENTURY (CLIPPINGS)., Folder 6 (Box Box 88)
  - TWENTIETH CENTURY (CLIPPINGS)., Folder 7 (Box Box 88)
  - TOWER BEHIND TRAGEDY (CLIPPINGS)., Folder 1 (Box Box 89)
  - THE TOWER BEYOND TRAGEDY., Folder 2 (Box Box 89)
  - GETTING MARRIED., Folder 3 (Box Box 89)
  - GETTING MARRIED., Folder 4 (Box Box 89)
  - GETTING MARRIED., Folder 5 (Box Box 89)
  - THE LITTLE BLUE LIGHT., Folder 6 (Box Box 89)
  - MARY ROSE (CLIPPINGS)., Folder 7 (Box Box 89)
  - MARY ROSE., Folder 8 (Box Box 89)
  - "NIGHT MUSIC"., Folder 90 (Box Box 1)
  - "PEER GYNT"., Folder 2 (Box Box 90)
  - PEER GYNT., Folder 3 (Box Box 90)
  - PEER GYNT., Folder 4 (Box Box 90)
  - FRENCH MEDIA (PARIS) OKLAHOMA (CLIPPINGS)., Folder 5 (Box Box 90)
  - FRENCH MEDIA (PARIS) PROGY AND BESS COMPANY., Folder 6 (Box Box 90)
  - WAR :- FILMS 1941 - 42., Folder 1 (Box Box 91)
  - THE PEACE - CLIPPINGS 1941 - 42., Folder 2 (Box Box 91)
  - WAR AND PEACE CLIPPINGS 1941 - 42., Folder 3 (Box Box 91)
  - WAR SIDE LIGHTS (CLIPPINGS REMOVED)., Folder 4 (Box Box 91)
  - (WAR) POST WAR PLANS., Folder 5 (Box Box 91)
  - WAR AND PEACE 1943., Folder 6 (Box Box 91)
  - WAR AND PEACE 1943 - 44., Folder 7 (Box Box 91)
  - NEWS CLIPPINGS - EXPORT OF CULTURE- EUROPEAN CULTURE ETC., Folder 8 (Box Box 91)
  - BREEN., Folder 9 (Box Box 91)
  - "GIN GAME" REVIEWS FROM VARIETY AND THE NY TIMES SAT. DEC, 8TH 1979., Folder 10 (Box Box 91)
  - WAR AND PEACE, DEMOCRACY AND FREEDOM FOR ALL ECT. MIS. NATIONALS., Folder 11 (Box Box 91)
  - SCRAPBOOK: ANTA PLAY SERIES., Folder 1 (Box Box 92)
  - POSTER BERLINER FESTIVAL., Folder 1 (Box Box 93)
  - SCRAPRBOOK 1945 AND 1947., Folder 1 (Box Box 94)
  - SCRAPBOOK 1946 AND IATSE STENCIL., Folder 1 (Box Box 95)
  - AMERICAN NATIONAL THEATER ALBUM., Folder 1 (Box Box 96)
  - ANTA ABLUM SUN. EVE. JAN. 29, 1950., Folder 2 (Box Box 96)
  - ANTA ALBUM OF STARS., Folder 3 (Box Box 96)
  - ANTA REVIEWS 1949., Folder 4 (Box Box 96)
  - ANTA NEWS CLIPPINGS 1950., Folder 5 (Box Box 96)
  - ANTA NEWS CLIPPINGS., Folder 6 (Box Box 96)
  - ZEIGFIELD THEATER SEATING PLAN., Folder 7 (Box Box 96)
  - HAMLET., Folder 1 (Box Box 97)
  - HAMLET., Folder 1 (Box Box 98)
  - HAMLET SOUND RECORDINGS., Folder 1 (Box Box 99)
  - HAMLET SOUND RECORDINGS., Folder 2 (Box Box 99)
  - HAMLET SOUND RECORDINGS., Folder 3 (Box Box 99)
  - HAMLET SOUND RECORDINGS., Folder 4 (Box Box 99)
  - HAMLET SOUND RECORDINGS., Folder 5 (Box Box 99)
  - HAMLET SOUND RECORDINGS., Folder 6 (Box Box 99)
  - HAMLET SOUND RECORDINGS., Folder 7 (Box Box 99)
  - HAMLET SOUND RECORDINGS., Folder 8 (Box Box 99)
  - HAMLET SOUND RECORDINGS., Folder 9 (Box Box 99)
  - HAMLET SOUND RECORDINGS., Folder 10 (Box Box 99)
  - HAMLET SOUND RECORDINGS., Folder 11 (Box Box 99)
  - HAMLET SOUND RECORDINGS., Folder 12 (Box Box 99)
  - HAMLET SOUND RECORDINGS., Folder 13 (Box Box 99)
  - HAMLET SOUND RECORDINGS., Folder 14 (Box Box 99)
  - HAMLET SOUND RECORDINGS., Folder 15 (Box Box 99)
  - HAMLET SOUND RECORDINGS., Folder 16 (Box Box 99)
  - BREEN SUPPLEMENTAL CHARTER (DATED 7/2/35) COPY., Folder 1 (Box Box 1)
  - RECONSTRUCTION FINANCE CORP. APPLICATION FOR A LOAN AND BACKGROUND MATERIAL., Folder 2 (Box Box 2)
  - DRAMATIC PRODUCTION CONTRACT: TOWER BEYOND TRAGEDY., Folder 3 (Box Box 100)
  - 1946 ANGELS., Folder 4 (Box Box 100)
  - COMMENDATION, U.S. SENATE, UNDATED., Folder 5 (Box Box 100)
  - LOUIS JOUVET NEWS CLIPPINGS., Folder 1 (Box Box 101)
  - LOUIS JOUVET NEWS CLIPPINGS., Folder 2 (Box Box 101)
  - LOUIS JOUVET NEWS CLIPPINGS., Folder 3 (Box Box 101)
  - LOUIS JOUVET NEWS CLIPPINGS., Folder 4 (Box Box 101)
  - LOUIS JOUVET NEWS CLIPPINGS., Folder 5 (Box Box 101)
  - LOUIS JOUVET NEWS CLIPPINGS., Folder 6 (Box Box 101)
  - SCRAPBOOK - FAUST PLUS HAMLET., Folder 7 (Box Box 101)
  - SCRAPBOOK - FAUST PLUS HAMLET., Folder 8 (Box Box 101)
  - LETTER (WILVA) TO ROBERT., Folder 1 (Box Box 102)
  - ANTA LETTER HEAD., Folder 2 (Box Box 102)
  - LETTER - AUTHURE PETERSON TO ROBERT BREEN 5/2/46., Folder 3 (Box Box 102)
  - HAMLET., Folder 4 (Box Box 102)
  - LETTER - LT. GEN JOHN K. CANNON TO BLEVINS DAVIS., Folder 5 (Box Box 102)
  - ANTA NEWSLETTER 11/1/49., Folder 6 (Box Box 102)
  - NEWS CLIPPINGS., Folder 7 (Box Box 102)
  - NEWS CLIPPINGS (ORIGINALS)., Folder 8 (Box Box 102)
  - AUDIENCE BUILDING - (PHOTOCOPIES)., Folder 9 (Box Box 102)
  - AUDIENCE BUILDING (ORIGINAL)., Folder 10 (Box Box 102)
  - ANTA PRESS RELEASE., Folder 11 (Box Box 102)
  - "GETTING MARRIED" G. B. SHAW., Folder 12 (Box Box 102)
  - AMERICAN NATIONAL BALLET THEATER TOUR OF EUROPE., Folder 13 (Box Box 102)